You don't know what you've got 'til it's...
Gone Girl is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by David Fincher.
With his wife's disappearance having become the focus of an intense media circus, a man sees
the spotlight turned on him when it's suspected that he may not be innocent.
Nick Dunne, played by Ben Affleck.
Amy Dunne, played by Rosamund Pike.
Desi Collings, played by Neil Patrick Harris.
Tanner Bolt, played by Tyler Perry.
Margo Dunne, played by Carrie Coon.
Detective Rhonda Boney, played by Kim Dickens.
Gone Girl is a 2014 American psychological thriller film directed by David Fincher and
written by Gillian Flynn, based on her 2012 novel of the same name.
It stars Ben Affleck, Rosamund Pike, Neil Patrick Harris,
Tyler Perry, and Carrie Coon in her film debut.
In the film, Nick Dunne (Affleck) becomes the prime suspect in the
sudden disappearance of his wife Amy (Pike) in Missouri.
Gone Girl premiered as the opening film at the 52nd New York Film Festival on September 26, 2014, and
was theatrically released in the United States on October 3, 2014, by 20th Century Fox.
The film received positive reviews from critics
and grossed $370 million worldwide.
It became Fincher's highest-grossing film and is
considered a cult postmodern mystery.
Gone Girl earned Pike numerous nominations including the Academy Award for Best Actress, the BAFTA Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role, the Critics' Choice Movie Award for Best
Actress, the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Drama, and the Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by a Female Actor in a Leading Role.
The film explores themes of infidelity, based on novel or
book, wife, marriage crisis, investigation.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.